I would be remiss if I did not bring up what we all know has been happening and the comments made
by coach Dawn Staley addressing an issue that I particularly feel passionate about as well.
When you look at how these ladies are playing the game, you talk about the trash talking,
you talk about their ability to make money now, we have to start making this an even playing field,
leveling the playing field with how we cover these young women and especially the African-American
women. Coach Staley was absolutely right. She was specifically talking about her team but I think
throughout the sport of women's basketball, it is our responsibility to talk about the game in a way
that empowers these women. When you see a young Angel Reese that has her lashes, her hair and her
physicality, it should be a beautiful thing and when we talk about her, it shouldn't be a thing of
she's bullying, it should be a thing of she's dominating, she's inspiring a team, she's fierce
passionate. Because when we talk about Caitlin, we give those same words but we give them a different
way because we see her uplifting her team. So I'm calling on everybody and our sister down there
in South Carolina that's built a dynasty, she was speaking truth to the game and she's going to keep
leading and I want all of us up here to say how we spoke about the women today, do better y'all,
everybody do better.